Guide to the Robert C. Calfee Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Robert C. Calfee papers
1964-1979
SC0226
Calfee, Robert C.
6 Linear feet
Office files regarding Calfee's position as Associate Dean of Research and Development, School of Education, and Director of the Stanford Center for Research and Development in Teaching.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Gift of Professor Robert Calfee, 1980.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
Professor of Education at Stanford (1969- ).
Description of the Collection
Office files regarding Calfee's position as Associate Dean of Research and Development, School of Education, and Director of the Stanford Center for Research and Development in Teaching.
Access Terms
Calfee, Robert C.; Calfee, Robert C.; Stanford Center for Research and Development in Teaching.; Stanford University. Graduate School of Education. Faculty.; Stanford University. Graduate School of Education. -- General subdivision--Faculty.
Collection Contents
- Papers
  - ERIC files, Clearinghouse on Teacher Education, 1968-1976 (Box 1)
  - R&D Memorandums and occasional papers, 1971-1978 (Box 2)
  - School of Education Files, 1964-1973 (Box 3a)
  - School of Education Files, 1968-1979 (Box 3b)
  - NIE files, 1978 -1979 (Box 4a)
  - ERIC Clearinghouse files, 1972-1974 (Box 4b)
  - R&D Memorandullls and Occasional Papcrs, 1971-1975 (Box 5)
  - NIE Files, 1976-1978 (Box 6a)
  - NIE Files, 1974-1978 (Box 6b)
  - NIE Files, 1975-1978 (Box 7a)
  - NIE Files, 1973-1978 (Box 7b)
  - Stanfond Center for nesearch and Development in Teaching, Reports and Publications, 1969-1976 (Box 8a)
  - Stanford Center for Research and Dcvelopment in Teaching, Proposal to Establish Center and the Annual Reports of the Center, 1964-1970 (Box 8b)